/*
File comtaining the dummy data to display on the web application
 */

export const data = [
  {
    question:"AFFINITY SALES",
    answer:"Selling insurance through groups such as professional and business associations",
  },
  {
    question:"ADMITTED COMPANY",
    answer:"An insurance company licensed and authorized to do business in a particular state",
  },
  {
    question:"ACTUAL CASH VALUE",
    answer:"A form of insurance that pays damages equal to the replacement value of damaged property minus depreciation",
  },
  {
    question:"ALLIED LINES",
    answer:"Property insurance that is usually bought in conjunction with fire insurance; it includes wind, water damage, and vandalism coverage.",
  },
  {
    question:"ANNUITANT",
    answer:"The person(s) who receives the income from an annuity contract. Usually the owner of the contract or his or her spouse",
  },
  {
    question:"ANNUITIZATION",
    answer:"The conversion of the account balance of a deferred annuity contract to income payments",
  },
  {
    question:"ANNUITY BENEFICIARY",
    answer:"In certain types of annuities, a person who receives annuity contract payments if the annuity owner or annuitant dies while payments are still due",
  },
  {
    question:"ANNUITY ISSUER",
    answer:"The insurance company that issues the annuity",
  },
  {
    question:"ANNUITY PROSPECTUS",
    answer:"Legal document providing detailed information about variable annuity contracts. Must be offered to each prospective buyer",
  },
  {
    question:"APPRAISAL",
    answer:"A survey to determine a property√≠s insurable value, or the amount of a loss",
  }
];
